[Music]
it takes one second for life to stand
still for questions to start building up
for Hope to turn into despair
for choices to be altered for life
itself to never be the same
just one second is all it takes for life
to take a critical turn
that is why we decided to stand by our
customers and ensure their protection
even in the toughest of times
with a protection that doesn't stop at
critical times
presenting ICICI Lombard tradition Plus
a plan that gives our customers Extra
Protection without compromises which
offers them coverage for 92 critical
illnesses
106 surgical procedures a multi-claim
option along with optional coverages for
personal accidents cancer restore so get
ready to make a new promise of
protection to our customers
and enable them to lead a worry-free
life
one plan that provides protection that
doesn't stop
[Music]